<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<article xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" version="5.0">
  <info>
    <author>Jianqing Guan and Aaron W. Hsu</author>
    <date>Wednesday, September 25th, 2013</date>
  </info>
  <section>
    <title>Statement of Work</title>
    <para>
     The goal of this project is to create a automatically grading system which enhances the current one for C211 to all courses in the university. 
    </para>
    <simpara>
      The MAGS (McKelvey Autograding System) is the current system used by
      the C211 Introduction to Computing course at Indiana University. This
      first version used by the class works well, but has limitations and
      bugs which have not been addressed or fixed during its lifetime.
      A new version of MAGS which scales to multiple classrooms and courses,
      as well as languages and systems should be developed. This project
      will create this new version, enhancing the existing system to include
      better student management, roster management, grade reporting, and
      handling of multiple class sections. 
    </simpara>
    <simpara>
      The application developed should be accessible through multiple
      channels, be clearly and easily extensible without affecting the
      overall stability of the system, and should be supportable by a single
      developer or associate instructor for the entire school, without much
      effort from the specific classes or courses being necessary.
      Additionally, the application should be open-source and available
      publically for use by other Universities. 
    </simpara>
    <simpara>
      In addition to the above, this project will create a number of
      documents with the express intent and purpose of ensuring the
      maintainability and longevity of the project. This means that the
      project should be able to continue even if there exists a long period
      of inactivity or if there is a discontinuity of the development team
      which might normally lead to a loss of expertise in the system. That
      is, it should be possible for a new developer to enter the system and
      learn how to use and work and develop the system without the
      mentorship of an existing developer if at all possible. 
    </simpara>
  </section>
</article>
